{
    "id": "09549a08a98e40109cddcbbd74e46fcb",
    "title": "Already And Yet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She has not ………………… started working on the project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13262f7f6bb6494c90daa32521b8d7ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………….. sent the payment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "972f719f7a034072a1d7e1ed22c43aeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "As …………………, I haven’t had time to talk to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39a5c5cd9b3744279ab7617108afe543"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have …………………. finished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1279fdc69d944e80bb86a34429f27862"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was tired, ………………….. he didn’t give up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3cd7fd1a71a64321829da91981f3a0bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The invitees have ………………….. turned up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b20ade279e214daf9dfb257d68806eb3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was surprised that they had ………………….. finished the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c017f351807f4eb8bb52ce193a2b0d14"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was surprised that she had ………………….. to start working on that project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c98af3f5d92c4b83b025466eae90f11d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government has …………………. to approve the project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "55477b7c22c746a7a35b9ad717044f12"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………… had enough.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51e88fe4bd1a49cb9491b52a1470d178"
        }
    ]
}